<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<job-search>
  <jobs total="5847" count="10" start="0">
    <job>
      <id>3751980</id>
      <company>
        <id>2761</id>
        <name>Emerson Network Power</name>
      </company>
      <job-poster>
        <id>WHx5IAcn9j</id>
        <first-name>Bobbi</first-name>
        <last-name>S.</last-name>
        <headline>Senior Corporate Recruiter - Emerson Network Power</headline>
      </job-poster>
      <description-snippet>Emerson Network Power, a business of Emerson and a global leader in protecting and optimizing critical infrastructure, is currently seeking a Sr Design Engineer -Software (Algorithm Development Engineer) for its Liebert AC power business in Delaware, OH.   Software Engineering position, involving designing and developing algorithms for embedded controls, system monitoring and fault diagnostics of </description-snippet>
      <location-description>Delaware, Ohio</location-description>
    </job>
    <job>
      <id>3765577</id>
      <company>
        <id>1349711</id>
        <name>ADB Airfield Solutions</name>
      </company>
      <job-poster>
        <id>0dNygwEzMi</id>
        <first-name>Kelly</first-name>
        <last-name>(.</last-name>
        <headline>HR Manager at ADB Airfield Solutions (Formerly Siemens Airfield Solutions)</headline>
      </job-poster>
      <description-snippet>Light up your career.  People discover the world thanks to ADBs Airfield Ground Lighting Systems, which offers safe visual guidance to pilots during take-off and landing in more than 2000 airports worldwide. As we are a medium sized company with international presence, ADB creates a professional environment where people with a passion for technology can make a real contribution to the airfield li</description-snippet>
      <location-description>Columbus, Ohio Area</location-description>
    </job>
    <job>
      <id>3645751</id>
      <company>
        <id>5725</id>
        <name>Ball Aerospace</name>
      </company>
      <salary>Competitive with excellent benefits!</salary>
      <job-poster>
        <id>503WgcHF3O</id>
        <first-name>Denise</first-name>
        <last-name>F.</last-name>
        <headline>Corporate Recruiter - Ball Aerospace &amp; Technologies Corp.</headline>
      </job-poster>
      <description-snippet>   Engineer II (Software Engineer)   What you'll do:   This position encompasses research &amp;amp; development (R&amp;amp;D) within the Warfighter Readiness Division's Distributed Mission Operations Training Research Testbeds.  The position requires a dedicated and experienced Software Engineer to work as part of a leading edge research and engineering, design and development team.  A primary responsibil</description-snippet>
      <location-description>Fairborn, OH</location-description>
    </job>
    <job>
      <id>3770206</id>
      <company>
        <id>2761</id>
        <name>Emerson Network Power</name>
      </company>
      <job-poster>
        <id>WHx5IAcn9j</id>
        <first-name>Bobbi</first-name>
        <last-name>S.</last-name>
        <headline>Senior Corporate Recruiter - Emerson Network Power</headline>
      </job-poster>
      <description-snippet>Emerson Network Power, a business of Emerson and a global leader in protecting and optimizing critical infrastructure, is currently seeking a Project Engineer - Software for its Liebert precision cooling business in Columbus, OH.   The Project Engineer- Software will provide technical leadership for software development.  This includes system design and coding.   ESSENTIAL FUNCTIONS:  Assigns and</description-snippet>
      <location-description>Columbus, Ohio</location-description>
    </job>
    <job>
      <id>3793423</id>
      <company>
        <id>7905</id>
        <name>RCI Recruitment Solutions</name>
      </company>
      <salary>$90K</salary>
      <job-poster>
        <id>oykc9J130w</id>
        <first-name>Kristine</first-name>
        <last-name>L.</last-name>
        <headline>Client Services Manager at RCI</headline>
      </job-poster>
      <description-snippet>Software Developer (Product Engineer) This position is primarily responsible for the software application and development processes to analyze, design, develop, test, implement and enhance software products. The Software Developer will provide technical leadership for software development.  This includes system design and coding. ESSENTIAL FUNCTIONS To perform this job successfully, an individual </description-snippet>
      <location-description>Columbus, OH</location-description>
    </job>
    <job>
      <id>3684497</id>
      <company>
        <id>1711</id>
        <name>Infor</name>
      </company>
      <salary>DOE</salary>
      <job-poster>
        <id>Nch-ElQ7f6</id>
        <first-name>Paula</first-name>
        <last-name>S.</last-name>
        <headline>Corporate Recruiter at Infor</headline>
      </job-poster>
      <description-snippet>JOB POSITION:  Software Engineer                         JOB LOCATION:       Columbus, OH                         JOB SUMMARY:  We are looking for 3 Software Engineers to do Application Development on our SyteLine Product in our Columbus office.  The Development will be SQL and VB.Net JOB RESPONSIBILITIES:   Construct code based on software designs.   Collaborate with team members for best-of-br</description-snippet>
      <location-description>Columbus</location-description>
    </job>
    <job>
      <id>3483084</id>
      <company>
        <id>1711</id>
        <name>Infor</name>
      </company>
      <job-poster>
        <id>dc3a7j_vyS</id>
        <first-name>Joe</first-name>
        <last-name>R.</last-name>
        <headline>Sr. Technical Recruiter at Infor</headline>
      </job-poster>
      <description-snippet>JOB SUMMARY:   We are looking for 3 Software Engineers to do Application Development on our SyteLine Product in our Columbus office.  The Development will be SQL and VB.Net    JOB RESPONSIBILITIES: Construct code based on software designs. Collaborate with team members for best-of-breed designs with a focus on scalability, upgrade-ability, maintainability, flexibility, extensibility, robustness wh</description-snippet>
      <location-description>Columbus, OH</location-description>
    </job>
    <job>
      <id>3663125</id>
      <company>
        <id>24141</id>
        <name>Astute Solutions</name>
      </company>
      <job-poster>
        <id>oCyXY1G2-A</id>
        <first-name>Ken</first-name>
        <last-name>T.</last-name>
        <headline>Sr Director of Product Development at Astute Solutions</headline>
      </job-poster>
      <description-snippet>In this position you will be responsible for defining and developing software changes, participate in architecture design teams and develop original and creative technical solutions meeting scalability, security, quality, and performance requirements. Duties &amp;amp; Responsibilities: Design, modify, develop, and write software applications      Responsible for analyzing the requirements for new prod</description-snippet>
      <location-description>Columbus, Ohio Area</location-description>
    </job>
    <job>
      <id>3534804</id>
      <company>
        <id>1009</id>
        <name>IBM</name>
      </company>
      <job-poster>
        <id>K9yMrUcSMq</id>
        <first-name>Michael</first-name>
        <last-name>K.</last-name>
        <headline>Recruiting Account Manager- IBM STG</headline>
      </job-poster>
      <description-snippet>Job descriptionWe are looking for motivated entry-level Software Engineers to join our development, quality assurance, and information development teams. This position is a tremendous opportunity to grow your skills in a very dynamic market and environment. You will be involved with the creation of UI and server products using cutting-edge technologies in a fast growing market with lots of upside </description-snippet>
      <location-description>Dublin, OH</location-description>
    </job>
    <job>
      <id>3492809</id>
      <company>
        <id>1519149</id>
        <name>Rumbo</name>
      </company>
      <salary>To be negotiated ( up to 30k)</salary>
      <job-poster>
        <id>dhep3KWLjb</id>
        <first-name>David</first-name>
        <last-name>C.</last-name>
        <headline>Director de RRHH en Rumbo.com</headline>
      </job-poster>
      <description-snippet>Responsibilities Collaborate in a specific Team guided by an experienced Team Leader. Participate in the analysis, development and maintenance of Javascript applications. Contributing to the planning and analyzing of high-level software strategies and solutions through functional and technical expertise. Designing and implementing analyses that will identify requirements related to people, process</description-snippet>
      <location-description>Madrid y alrededores, Espa?a</location-description>
    </job>
  </jobs>
  <num-results>5847</num-results>
  <facets total="1">
    <facet>
      <code>company</code>
      <name>Company</name>
      <buckets total="11">
        <bucket>
          <code>1035</code>
          <name>Microsoft</name>
          <count>978</count>
          <selected>false</selected>
        </bucket>
        <bucket>
          <code>21836</code>
          <name>CyberCoders</name>
          <count>609</count>
          <selected>false</selected>
        </bucket>
        <bucket>
          <code>1586</code>
          <name>Amazon</name>
          <count>200</count>
          <selected>false</selected>
        </bucket>
        <bucket>
          <code>1441</code>
          <name>Google</name>
          <count>143</count>
          <selected>false</selected>
        </bucket>
        <bucket>
          <code>3608</code>
          <name>NVIDIA</name>
          <count>103</count>
          <selected>false</selected>
        </bucket>
        <bucket>
          <code>2017</code>
          <name>Qualcomm</name>
          <count>87</count>
          <selected>false</selected>
        </bucket>
        <bucket>
          <code>1063</code>
          <name>Cisco Systems</name>
          <count>73</count>
          <selected>false</selected>
        </bucket>
        <bucket>
          <code>1449</code>
          <name>Electronic Arts</name>
          <count>73</count>
          <selected>false</selected>
        </bucket>
        <bucket>
          <code>2751</code>
          <name>Expedia</name>
          <count>71</count>
          <selected>false</selected>
        </bucket>
        <bucket>
          <code>1614</code>
          <name>SAIC</name>
          <count>70</count>
          <selected>false</selected>
        </bucket>
        <bucket>
          <code>3672</code>
          <name>CACI International Inc</name>
          <count>67</count>
          <selected>false</selected>
        </bucket>
      </buckets>
    </facet>
  </facets>
</job-search>
